Sep 23, 2024 | 5:22 PM EDT
    
    ### [Valve appears to be testing ARM support for Steam games](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/23/valve-appears-to-be-testing-arm-support-for-steam-games/)

    Sep 23, 2024 | 3:32 PM EDT
    
    ### [Linkin Park to perform 2024 League of Legends Championship Anthem](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/23/linkin-park-league-of-legends-championship-anthem/)

    Sep 23, 2024 | 12:49 PM EDT
    
    ### [PlayStation State of Play returns Sept. 24, featuring over 20 games](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/23/playstation-state-of-play-september-24-2024-over-20-games/)

    Sep 22, 2024 | 11:03 AM EDT
    
    ### [The GameSir G8 Plus is great to use with my Pixel 9 Pro Fold](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/22/gamesir-g8-plus-foldable/)

    Sep 20, 2024 | 4:37 PM EDT
    
    ### [Netflix Games adds Civilization VI, Street Fighter IV and more](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/20/netflix-games-civilization-vi-street-fighter-iv/)

    Sep 19, 2024 | 4:08 PM EDT
    
    ### [Nintendo and The Pokémon Company have finally sued Palworld developer Pocketpair](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/19/nintendo-the-pokemon-company-palworld-developer-pocketpair-lawsuit/)

        Sep 23, 2024 | 5:22 PM EDT
        
        ### [Valve appears to be testing ARM support for Steam games](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/23/valve-appears-to-be-testing-arm-support-for-steam-games/)

        Sep 23, 2024 | 3:32 PM EDT
        
        ### [Linkin Park to perform 2024 League of Legends Championship Anthem](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/23/linkin-park-league-of-legends-championship-anthem/)

        Sep 23, 2024 | 12:49 PM EDT
        
        ### [PlayStation State of Play returns Sept. 24, featuring over 20 games](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/23/playstation-state-of-play-september-24-2024-over-20-games/)

        Sep 22, 2024 | 11:03 AM EDT
        
        ### [The GameSir G8 Plus is great to use with my Pixel 9 Pro Fold](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/22/gamesir-g8-plus-foldable/)

        Sep 20, 2024 | 4:37 PM EDT
        
        ### [Netflix Games adds Civilization VI, Street Fighter IV and more](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/20/netflix-games-civilization-vi-street-fighter-iv/)

        Sep 19, 2024 | 4:08 PM EDT
        
        ### [Nintendo and The Pokémon Company have finally sued Palworld developer Pocketpair](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/19/nintendo-the-pokemon-company-palworld-developer-pocketpair-lawsuit/)

    Sep 24, 2024 | 3:35 PM EDT
    
    ### [QueerTech brings annual QT conference to Toronto from Nov. 6-7](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/24/queertech-conference/)

    Sep 24, 2024 | 2:45 PM EDT
    
    ### [Logitech moves beyond keyboards with the MX Creative Console](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/24/logitech-moves-beyond-keyboards-with-the-mx-creative-console/)

    Sep 24, 2024 | 1:30 PM EDT
    
    ### [Google Photos getting AI-powered video editing tools in new update](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/24/google-photos-video-editing-tools-new-update/)

    Sep 24, 2024 | 12:40 PM EDT
    
    ### [HP details new laptops at Imagine 2024](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/24/hp-new-laptops-imagine-2024/)

    Sep 24, 2024 | 12:28 PM EDT
    
    ### [Cineplex ordered to pay $38.9 million over ‘deceptive’ online booking fees](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/24/cineplex-fined-nearly-40-million-dollars-deceptive-online-booking-fees/)

    Sep 24, 2024 | 9:55 AM EDT
    
    ### [Amazon Key In-Garage delivery now available in over 1,700 Canadian cities and towns](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/24/amazon-key-in-garage-delivery-available-canada/)

        Sep 23, 2024 | 10:38 AM EDT
        
        ### [Some former Koodo customers reportedly got $15/50GB 4G win-back deal](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/23/koodo-win-back-15-50gb-4g-plan/)

        Sep 19, 2024 | 12:53 PM EDT
        
        ### [PSA: Watch out for 2FA phishing texts pretending to be from Rogers](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/19/psa-watch-out-for-phishing-scam-texts-rogers/)

        Sep 18, 2024 | 3:49 PM EDT
        
        ### [SaskTel seeks judicial review of CRTC wholesale fibre access decision](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/18/sasktel-judicial-review-crtc-wholesale-access-fibre-decision/)

        Sep 18, 2024 | 12:30 PM EDT
        
        ### [Statistics Canada changes how it tracks wireless pricing](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/18/statistics-canada-changes-wireless-pricing-tracking/)

        Sep 18, 2024 | 11:11 AM EDT
        
        ### [Rogers buys out Bell stake in Leafs, Raptors parent company MLSE \[Update\]](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/18/rogers-buys-out-bell-stake-leaf-raptors-mlse/)

        Sep 17, 2024 | 3:48 PM EDT
        
        ### [Bell, MacLean collaborate on remote mining vehicle technology](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/17/bell-maclean-mining-technology-collaboration/)

        Sep 23, 2024 | 4:13 PM EDT
        
        ### [iPhone 17 and iPhone 17 Air rumoured to feature 120Hz refresh rate](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/23/iphone-17-air-120hz-refresh-rate/)

        Sep 20, 2024 | 3:34 PM EDT
        
        ### [Huawei’s tri-folding phone launches in global markets in Q1 2025: report](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/20/huawei-tri-folding-global-markets-q1/)

        Sep 20, 2024 | 11:36 AM EDT
        
        ### [28 Years Later will be the biggest movie ever shot on iPhone: report](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/20/28-years-later-shot-on-iphone-15-pro-report/)

        Sep 19, 2024 | 4:48 PM EDT
        
        ### [Here’s how the iPhone 16 series battery holds up compared to iPhone 15](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/19/iphone-16-vs-15-battery-life-comparison/)

        Sep 19, 2024 | 3:44 PM EDT
        
        ### [Another rumour points to Android 15 rolling out on October 15](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/19/android-15-rolling-out-october-15/)

        Sep 17, 2024 | 1:54 PM EDT
        
        ### [Samsung Galaxy S25+ reportedly thinner with same battery](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/17/samsung-galaxy-s25-plus-thinner-same-battery/)

        Sep 24, 2024 | 12:40 PM EDT
        
        ### [HP details new laptops at Imagine 2024](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/24/hp-new-laptops-imagine-2024/)

        Sep 17, 2024 | 5:07 PM EDT
        
        ### [Apple pulls iPadOS 18 for M4 iPad Pro after bricking reports](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/17/apple-pulls-ipados-18-m4-ipad-pro-bricking-reports/)

        Sep 12, 2024 | 11:56 AM EDT
        
        ### [Samsung Galaxy Tab S10+ rumoured to launch on September 26](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/12/samsung-galaxy-tab-s10-plus-september-26/)

        Sep 4, 2024 | 10:18 AM EDT
        
        ### [Asus unveils various Intel Core Ultra Series 2 laptops](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/04/asus-intel-core-ultra-series-2/)

        Sep 4, 2024 | 7:00 AM EDT
        
        ### [Asus announces Vivo S 15 and ProArt PZ13 laptops powered by Snapdragon X Plus](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/04/asus-vivo-s-15-proart-pz13-laptops/)

        Sep 3, 2024 | 3:41 PM EDT
        
        ### [Intel says its new chips will get Copilot Plus PC features via a free update in November](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/03/intel-lunar-lake-copilot-pc-feature-update-november/)

        Sep 24, 2024 | 1:30 PM EDT
        
        ### [Google Photos getting AI-powered video editing tools in new update](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/24/google-photos-video-editing-tools-new-update/)

        Sep 24, 2024 | 12:28 PM EDT
        
        ### [Cineplex ordered to pay $38.9 million over ‘deceptive’ online booking fees](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/24/cineplex-fined-nearly-40-million-dollars-deceptive-online-booking-fees/)

        Sep 24, 2024 | 9:00 AM EDT
        
        ### [Spotify expands AI Playlist beta feature to Canada](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/24/spotify-ai-playlist-canada/)

        Sep 23, 2024 | 5:22 PM EDT
        
        ### [Valve appears to be testing ARM support for Steam games](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/23/valve-appears-to-be-testing-arm-support-for-steam-games/)

        Sep 20, 2024 | 12:34 PM EDT
        
        ### [iOS 18.1 public beta now available with some Apple Intelligence features](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/20/ios-18-1-public-beta-now-available-apple-intelligence/)

        Sep 18, 2024 | 4:40 PM EDT
        
        ### [Forget Geico: New Telus subscription promises up to 15 percent savings on energy bills](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/18/telus-smartenergy-subscription-save-energy-bills/)

        Sep 24, 2024 | 9:55 AM EDT
        
        ### [Amazon Key In-Garage delivery now available in over 1,700 Canadian cities and towns](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/24/amazon-key-in-garage-delivery-available-canada/)

        Aug 28, 2024 | 10:45 AM EDT
        
        ### [Here are Sonos’ July and August update patch notes](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/08/28/sonos-app-fixes-july-august/)

        Aug 8, 2024 | 9:00 AM EDT
        
        ### [Sonos delaying two products until it fixes app](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/08/08/sonos-delaying-two-products-until-it-fixes-app/)

        Aug 6, 2024 | 4:38 PM EDT
        
        ### [New Google TV set-top box has enough power to kill the Chromecast](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/08/06/new-google-tv-set-top-box-canada-price/)

        Aug 6, 2024 | 2:03 PM EDT
        
        ### [New Nest Thermostat improves the design, compatibility and more](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/08/06/new-nest-thermostat-design-compatibility-canada/)

        Jul 29, 2024 | 4:13 PM EDT
        
        ### [Leaked renders reveal Google’s 4th-gen Nest Learning Thermostat](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/07/29/google-4th-gen-nest-learning-thermostat-leak/)

        Sep 20, 2024 | 10:19 AM EDT
        
        ### [Prototype solid-state battery ups energy density almost 25 percent compared to lithium-ion](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/20/solid-state-battery-prototype-increased-energy-density/)

        Sep 6, 2024 | 4:03 PM EDT
        
        ### [Next Android Auto update may make it easier to play the radio](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/06/upcoming-android-auto-update-play-music-local-storage-radio/)

        Aug 9, 2024 | 1:38 PM EDT
        
        ### [Tesla launches Cybertruck in Canada, starting at nearly $140,000](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/08/09/tesla-cybertruck-launch-canada/)

        Aug 7, 2024 | 4:16 PM EDT
        
        ### [First Tesla Cybertruck fatality reported after crash and fire](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/08/07/first-tesla-cybertruck-fatality-report/)

        Jul 30, 2024 | 4:09 PM EDT
        
        ### [Google’s Project Green Light uses Maps, AI to optimize traffic lights](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/07/30/google-project-green-light-maps-ai-optimize-traffic-lights/)

        Jul 18, 2024 | 10:07 AM EDT
        
        ### [Ford no longer making EVs in Oakville, transitions to trucks instead](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/07/18/ford-ev-oakville-factory-trucks/)

        Sep 24, 2024 | 2:45 PM EDT
        
        ### [Logitech moves beyond keyboards with the MX Creative Console](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/24/logitech-moves-beyond-keyboards-with-the-mx-creative-console/)

        Sep 20, 2024 | 2:34 PM EDT
        
        ### [Google scraps Pixel Buds’ shortcut to make Assistant read notifications](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/20/google-pixel-buds-assistant-read-notifications-removal/)

        Sep 13, 2024 | 2:46 PM EDT
        
        ### [PSA: 41mm Pixel Watch bands won’t work with the 45mm Pixel Watch 3](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/13/psa-41mm-pixel-watch-bands-wont-work-with-the-45mm-pixel-watch-3/)

        Sep 5, 2024 | 10:59 AM EDT
        
        ### [Bluetooth 6.0 arrives to improve location trackers and smart locks](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/05/bluetooth-6-0-improve-location-trackers-smart-lock/)

        Aug 30, 2024 | 9:49 AM EDT
        
        ### [Apple TV+ to get directors cut of Napoleon, more immersive videos in September](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/08/30/apple-directors-cut-napoleon-immersive-videos-wolfs/)

        Aug 27, 2024 | 1:00 PM EDT
        
        ### [Sony pushes further into PC market with new PlayStation Accessories app](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/08/27/sony-pc-market-playstation-accessories-app-dualsense/)

        Sep 24, 2024 | 9:01 AM EDT
        
        ### [Roku Ultra + Voice Remote bundle is now available for pre-order](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/24/roku-ultra-voice-remote-bundle/)

        Sep 20, 2024 | 1:33 PM EDT
        
        ### [Arcane’s final season gets staggered release on Netflix in November](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/20/netflix-arcane-november-final-season-staggered-release/)

        Sep 19, 2024 | 4:33 PM EDT
        
        ### [MrBeast and Amazon sued by contestants over Beast Games series](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/19/mrbeast-amazon-sued-contestants-beast-games-series/)

        Sep 17, 2024 | 3:01 PM EDT
        
        ### [Heartstopper season 3 trailer reveals October 3 release date](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/17/heartstopper-season-3-trailer-october-3/)

        Sep 9, 2024 | 12:52 PM EDT
        
        ### [Studio Ghibli’s The Boy and the Heron hits Netflix Canada in October](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/09/studio-ghibli-hayao-miyazaki-the-boy-and-the-heron-netflix-canada-premiere-date/)

        Aug 28, 2024 | 12:22 PM EDT
        
        ### [New on Paramount+ Canada: September 2024](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/08/28/paramount-plus-canada-new-content-september-2024/)

        Sep 20, 2024 | 12:34 PM EDT
        
        ### [iOS 18.1 public beta now available with some Apple Intelligence features](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/20/ios-18-1-public-beta-now-available-apple-intelligence/)

        Sep 18, 2024 | 2:55 PM EDT
        
        ### [Meta and Ray-Ban owner will work together into next decade](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/18/meta-ray-ban-next-decade/)

        Sep 16, 2024 | 4:28 PM EDT
        
        ### [Google’s Gemini Live rolling out for free to Android users in Canada](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/16/gemini-live-rolling-out-free-android-users-canada/)

        Sep 6, 2024 | 1:44 PM EDT
        
        ### [Google launches AI-powered Photos search in limited U.S. test](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/06/google-photos-ai-search-us-test/)

        Sep 4, 2024 | 3:11 PM EDT
        
        ### [Nova Scotia partners with Google Cloud on AI-powered healthcare solutions](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/04/nova-scotia-google-cloud-partnership-ai-powered-healthcare-solutions/)

        Aug 29, 2024 | 2:32 PM EDT
        
        ### [Testing Apple Intelligence in Canada gets easier with iOS 18.1 Developer Beta 3](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/08/29/testing-apple-intelligence-in-canada-gets-easier-with-ios-18-1-developer-beta-3/)

        Sep 23, 2024 | 10:38 AM EDT
        
        ### [Some former Koodo customers reportedly got $15/50GB 4G win-back deal](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/23/koodo-win-back-15-50gb-4g-plan/)

        Sep 17, 2024 | 10:39 AM EDT
        
        ### [Amazon Prime Big Deal Days returns October 8 and 9](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/17/amazon-prime-big-deal-day-october-8-9/)

        Sep 13, 2024 | 3:28 PM EDT
        
        ### [Get a free Apple Watch Series 10 with iPhone 16 pre-orders at Freedom](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/13/freedom-mobile-free-apple-watch-series-10-iphone-16-pre-orders/)

        Sep 6, 2024 | 2:45 PM EDT
        
        ### [Fido emailing former customers a $34/50GB win-back deal](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/06/fido-emailing-former-customers-34-50gb-win-back-deal/)

        Sep 5, 2024 | 5:15 PM EDT
        
        ### [Koodo offering six months of free Apple TV+ to some via text](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/05/koodo-offering-six-months-free-apple-tv/)

        Sep 3, 2024 | 10:29 AM EDT
        
        ### [Freedom now offering $10/mo Pixel 8 deal](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/03/freedom-mobile-pixel-8-deal/)

    Sep 22, 2024 | 11:03 AM EDT
    
    ### [The GameSir G8 Plus is great to use with my Pixel 9 Pro Fold](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/22/gamesir-g8-plus-foldable/)

    Sep 19, 2024 | 1:16 PM EDT
    
    ### [iPhone 16 series review: A camera built to give you control](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/19/iphone-16-series-review-a-camera-built-to-give-you-control/)

    Sep 18, 2024 | 9:28 PM EDT
    
    ### [iPhone 16 Pro series review in progress: Searching for the perfect shots](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/18/iphone-16-pro-series-review-camera-photographer-focused/)

    Sep 17, 2024 | 11:02 AM EDT
    
    ### [Apple Watch Series 10 Review: Big watch, big dreams 🤩💫](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/17/apple-watch-series-10-review-big-screen-tested/)

    Sep 16, 2024 | 8:09 AM EDT
    
    ### [Apple AirPods 4 review: A tale of two tones](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/16/apple-airpods-4-review-a-tale-of-two-tones/)

    Sep 11, 2024 | 7:30 PM EDT
    
    ### [iPhone 16 and 16 Pro hands-on: Camera Control for everyone](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/11/iphone-16-and-16-pro-hands-on-test-camera-control/)

        Sep 19, 2024 | 1:16 PM EDT
        
        ### [iPhone 16 series review: A camera built to give you control](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/19/iphone-16-series-review-a-camera-built-to-give-you-control/)

        Sep 18, 2024 | 9:28 PM EDT
        
        ### [iPhone 16 Pro series review in progress: Searching for the perfect shots](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/18/iphone-16-pro-series-review-camera-photographer-focused/)

        Sep 11, 2024 | 7:30 PM EDT
        
        ### [iPhone 16 and 16 Pro hands-on: Camera Control for everyone](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/11/iphone-16-and-16-pro-hands-on-test-camera-control/)

        Sep 9, 2024 | 10:51 AM EDT
        
        ### [The Honor Magic V3 is magically light and thin for a foldable](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/09/the-honor-magic-v3-is-magically-light-and-thin-for-a-foldable/)

        Sep 7, 2024 | 8:53 AM EDT
        
        ### [TCL Nxtpaper 50 Pro improves the e-ink display experience](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/07/tcl-nxtpaper-50-pro-hands-on/)

        Sep 3, 2024 | 1:00 PM EDT
        
        ### [Pixel 9 Pro Fold Review in Progress: Hard to put down](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/03/pixel-9-pro-fold-review-in-progress-hard-to-put-down/)

        Aug 24, 2024 | 11:03 AM EDT
        
        ### [Surface Pro (11th Edition) Review: Finally, a good ARM Surface](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/08/24/surface-pro-11th-edition-review/)

        Jul 23, 2024 | 8:31 AM EDT
        
        ### [Asus ROG Zephyrus G14 and G16 Review: Covert gaming](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/07/23/asus-rog-zephyrus-g14-g16-review-gaming-laptop-pc/)

        Jun 18, 2024 | 12:01 AM EDT
        
        ### [Early impressions of Qualcomm’s Snapdragon X Elite: Good, not great](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/06/18/early-impressions-snapdragon-x-elite-good-not-great/)

        Jun 2, 2024 | 11:03 AM EDT
        
        ### [iPad Air (M2) would have been a pro in any other year](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/06/02/ipad-air-m2-would-have-been-a-pro-in-any-other-year/)

        May 20, 2024 | 7:06 PM EDT
        
        ### [Hands-on with Microsoft’s Copilot + PC Surface Laptop and Pro](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/05/20/hands-on-microsofts-copilot-pc-surface-laptop-pro/)

        May 20, 2024 | 1:33 PM EDT
        
        ### [Microsoft announces new Surface devices, Copilot + PCs](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/05/20/microsoft-announces-new-surface-latop-and-pro/)

        Sep 10, 2024 | 1:49 PM EDT
        
        ### [Osim’s uLove3 has changed massage chairs and sitting forever](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/10/osim-ulove3-massage-chair/)

        Sep 7, 2024 | 2:29 PM EDT
        
        ### [JMGO N1S Ultimate 4K is an amazing projector, but it won’t be for everyone](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/07/jmgo-n1s-ultimate-4k-projector-review/)

        Sep 7, 2024 | 11:12 AM EDT
        
        ### [I still love Nanoleaf’s Umbra Cono and Cup smart lamps despite all the bugs](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/07/nanoleaf-umbra-cono-cup-smart-lamp-review/)

        Aug 30, 2024 | 12:41 PM EDT
        
        ### [The HomePod mini is the key to an Apple smart home](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/08/30/homepod-mini-replace-sonos-2024-review/)

        Aug 17, 2024 | 2:27 PM EDT
        
        ### [The Tineco Floor One S5 makes vacuuming and mopping so much more efficient](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/08/17/tineco-floor-one-s5-vacuum-mop-2-in-1-review/)

        Jun 23, 2024 | 2:03 PM EDT
        
        ### [Dangbei DBOX02 review: My first projector is a dream (but setting it up wasn’t)](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/06/23/dangbei-dbox02-review-my-first-projector-tips-tricks/)

        Sep 8, 2024 | 11:03 AM EDT
        
        ### [2025 Volvo EX90 test drive: Bigger, smoother, with bumps to work out](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/08/2025-volvo-ex90-test-drive/)

        May 16, 2024 | 2:28 PM EDT
        
        ### [Elon Musk’s Las Vegas Loop is a fun theme park ride in disguise](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/05/16/elon-musk-las-vegas-loop-review/)

        Feb 18, 2024 | 2:22 PM EST
        
        ### [Taking 70mai’s A810 dashcam for a drive was a great intro to the world of dashcams](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/02/18/70mai-a810-4k-dashcam-review/)

        Feb 14, 2024 | 6:45 PM EST
        
        ### [Lincoln’s Canadian-made ‘Digital Experience’ debuts in the 2024 Nautilus](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/02/14/lincoln-canadian-made-digital-experience-debuts-in-2024-nautilus/)

        Nov 21, 2023 | 7:01 AM EST
        
        ### [2025 Volvo EX30 Test Drive: Smooth ride centred on a screen](https://mobilesyrup.com/2023/11/21/2025-volvo-ex30-test-drive-smooth-ride-centred-on-a-screen/)

        May 29, 2023 | 3:20 PM EDT
        
        ### [After 20,000km with Hyundai’s Ioniq 5, here’s what you need to know before you buy](https://mobilesyrup.com/2023/05/29/hyundai-ioniq-5-ev-20000km-review/)

        Sep 9, 2024 | 1:00 PM EDT
        
        ### [Google Pixel Watch 3 Review: Bigger and better](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/09/google-pixel-watch-3-review/)

        Aug 23, 2024 | 5:07 PM EDT
        
        ### [OnePlus Nord Buds 3 Pro prove once again OnePlus makes great affordable buds](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/08/23/oneplus-nord-buds-3-pro-prove-once-again-oneplus-makes-great-affordable-buds/)

        Aug 6, 2024 | 7:58 AM EDT
        
        ### [The GameSir X4 Aileron is my favourite mobile controller](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/08/06/gamesir-x4-aileron-review/)

        Jul 21, 2024 | 2:29 PM EDT
        
        ### [The Logitech MX Keys has been my go-to keyboard for years](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/07/21/logitech-mx-keys-has-been-my-go-to-keyboard-for-years/)

        Jul 20, 2024 | 11:03 AM EDT
        
        ### [Razer’s Kishi Ultra controller is one of the best I’ve used](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/07/20/razer-kishi-ultra-review-gaming-controller/)

        Jul 14, 2024 | 2:23 PM EDT
        
        ### [This BenQ monitor proves 3:2 is the perfect computer aspect ratio](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/07/14/benq-monitor-rd280u-square-review/)

        Sep 22, 2024 | 11:03 AM EDT
        
        ### [The GameSir G8 Plus is great to use with my Pixel 9 Pro Fold](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/22/gamesir-g8-plus-foldable/)

        Sep 5, 2024 | 8:00 AM EDT
        
        ### [Astro Bot is one of the greatest PlayStation games of all time](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/05/astro-bot-ps5-review/)

        Sep 1, 2024 | 2:04 PM EDT
        
        ### [Age of Mythology Retold reminded me how much I like RTS games](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/01/age-of-mythology-retold-reminded-me-how-much-i-like-rts-games/)

        Aug 18, 2024 | 2:03 PM EDT
        
        ### [There’s no denying the Backbone controller is great for mobile gaming](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/08/18/backbone-mobile-gaming-controller-review/)

        Aug 4, 2024 | 11:06 AM EDT
        
        ### [Marvel Rivals is fun with potential, just needs some polish](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/08/04/marvel-rivals-fun-potential/)

        Jul 20, 2024 | 2:31 PM EDT
        
        ### [Capcom’s Kunitsu-Gami is one of the freshest new games in a while](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/07/20/capcom-kunitsu-gami-path-of-the-goddess-review/)

        Aug 21, 2024 | 1:02 PM EDT
        
        ### [Pixel Screenshots is an imperfect but surprisingly helpful app](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/08/21/pixel-screenshots-hands-on/)

        Jul 15, 2024 | 4:36 PM EDT
        
        ### [Embracing customization made the iOS Photos app so much better](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/07/15/ios-18-photos-app-customize-review-how-to/)

        Apr 11, 2024 | 9:07 PM EDT
        
        ### [Google Photos on Android to soon let users convert photos to save storage](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/04/11/google-photos-android-save-storage/)

        Mar 10, 2024 | 9:02 AM EDT
        
        ### [Here are some features I really like about the Arc browser on Windows](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/03/10/arc-windows-beta-favourite-features/)

        Dec 11, 2023 | 6:00 PM EST
        
        ### [Your iPhone just got a new Journal app – here’s how it works](https://mobilesyrup.com/2023/12/11/iphone-new-journal-app-how-it-works/)

        Jul 30, 2023 | 6:02 PM EDT
        
        ### [VSCO has been my favourite mobile app for over ten years](https://mobilesyrup.com/2023/07/30/vsco-mobile-photo-editing-app-review-2023-ios-apple-android/)

    Sep 19, 2024 | 11:51 AM EDT
    
    ### [YouTube’s new creation tools impressed me, even as someone who doesn’t make videos](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/19/made-on-youtube-2024-highlights-non-creator/)

    Sep 19, 2024 | 9:00 AM EDT
    
    ### [Microsoft Flight Simulator 2024 has already given me a greater appreciation of the planet](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/19/microsoft-flight-simulator-2024-preview/)

    Sep 15, 2024 | 2:32 PM EDT
    
    ### [Unpacking all the announcements from Apple’s fall iPhone event \[Video\]](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/15/unpacking-announcements-apple-fall-iphone-event-apple-watch-10-airpods-4/)

    Sep 9, 2024 | 9:00 AM EDT
    
    ### [Super Mario Party Jamboree is Mario Party at its best](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/09/super-mario-party-jamboree-nintendo-switch-preview/)

    Sep 6, 2024 | 12:49 PM EDT
    
    ### [Gaming legend Jennifer Hale on X-Men ’97, AI concerns and ‘extraordinary’ Canadian talent](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/06/jennifer-hale-interview-x-men-97-ai-canadian-talent/)

    Sep 6, 2024 | 10:04 AM EDT
    
    ### [There were a lot of impressive Canadian indie games at PAX West 2024](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/06/canadian-indie-games-pax-west-2024/)

        Aug 9, 2024 | 5:23 PM EDT
        
        ### [I used Freedom Mobile as my main SIM for 10 months, here’s how it went](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/08/09/freedom-mobile-10-month-test-canada-review/)

        May 2, 2024 | 9:42 AM EDT
        
        ### [Fido increases 60GB 4G plan by $4/mo](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/05/02/fido-increases-60gb-4g-plan-price/)

        Nov 12, 2023 | 4:02 PM EST
        
        ### [What it’s like to use an Apple Watch with cellular in Canada](https://mobilesyrup.com/2023/11/12/apple-watch-cellular-connecitivity-in-canada/)

        Oct 26, 2023 | 11:52 AM EDT
        
        ### [We tested Freedom Mobile’s 5G to see if it’s better than our current carriers](https://mobilesyrup.com/2023/10/26/testing-freedom-mobile-5g-network-canada/)

        Oct 9, 2023 | 11:00 AM EDT
        
        ### [Poor network connectivity? SureCall may help](https://mobilesyrup.com/2023/10/09/poor-network-connectivity-surecall-may-help/)

        Jul 25, 2023 | 7:04 PM EDT
        
        ### [Telecom providers play blame game as they agree to join fed’s TTC consultation](https://mobilesyrup.com/2023/07/25/telecom-providers-ttc-connectivity-consultation/)

        May 9, 2024 | 7:31 PM EDT
        
        ### [Are giant iPads the next big thing?](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/05/09/who-uses-big-ipads/)

        Mar 16, 2024 | 11:05 AM EDT
        
        ### [More games now include diverse characters, so losers are trying to start ‘Gamergate 2’](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/03/16/sweet-baby-controversy-toxic-gamers-stand-up-for-devs-and-media-editorial/)

        Mar 13, 2024 | 7:14 PM EDT
        
        ### [Here are all the things Netflix has taken from us](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/03/13/here-are-all-the-things-netflix-has-taken-from-us/)

        Jan 14, 2024 | 4:32 PM EST
        
        ### [Phone makers are loading their devices with AI, but is it AI people actually want?](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/01/14/are-phones-getting-good-ai/)

        Jan 13, 2024 | 11:02 AM EST
        
        ### [Suicide Squad: Kill the Justice League reiterates the dangers of chasing live service trends](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/01/13/suicide-squad-kill-the-justice-league-negative-previews-live-service-trend-editorial/)

        Jan 8, 2024 | 8:00 PM EST
        
        ### [Here’s why iPadOS and the iPad are far from prime time ready](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/01/08/heres-why-ipados-and-the-ipad-are-far-from-prime-time-ready/)

        Jan 14, 2024 | 1:30 PM EST
        
        ### [Here are the best accessories for the ultimate desk setup](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/01/14/here-are-all-the-best-accessories-for-the-ultimate-desk-setup/)

        Dec 6, 2023 | 7:12 PM EST
        
        ### [MobileSyrup’s Holiday Gift Guide \[2023 Edition\]](https://mobilesyrup.com/2023/12/06/mobilesyrup-holiday-gift-guide-2023-edition/)

        Dec 4, 2023 | 6:44 PM EST
        
        ### [MobileSyrup’s Nerd Gift Guide \[2023 Edition\]](https://mobilesyrup.com/2023/12/04/mobilesyrups-nerd-gift-guide-2023-edition/)

        Nov 25, 2023 | 2:00 PM EST
        
        ### [MobileSyrup’s Apple Accessory Gift Guide \[2023 Edition\]](https://mobilesyrup.com/2023/11/25/mobilesyrup-apple-accessory-gift-guide-2023-edition/)

        Aug 11, 2023 | 10:30 AM EDT
        
        ### [Back to School Gift Guide \[2023 Edition\]](https://mobilesyrup.com/2023/08/11/mobilesyrups-back-to-school-gift-guide-2023/)

        Jun 9, 2023 | 4:55 PM EDT
        
        ### [MobileSyrup’s Father’s Day Gift Guide \[2023 Edition\]](https://mobilesyrup.com/2023/06/09/mobilesyrups-fathers-day-gift-guide-2023-edition/)

        Sep 19, 2024 | 11:51 AM EDT
        
        ### [YouTube’s new creation tools impressed me, even as someone who doesn’t make videos](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/19/made-on-youtube-2024-highlights-non-creator/)

        Sep 19, 2024 | 9:00 AM EDT
        
        ### [Microsoft Flight Simulator 2024 has already given me a greater appreciation of the planet](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/19/microsoft-flight-simulator-2024-preview/)

        Sep 15, 2024 | 2:32 PM EDT
        
        ### [Unpacking all the announcements from Apple’s fall iPhone event \[Video\]](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/15/unpacking-announcements-apple-fall-iphone-event-apple-watch-10-airpods-4/)

        Sep 9, 2024 | 9:00 AM EDT
        
        ### [Super Mario Party Jamboree is Mario Party at its best](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/09/super-mario-party-jamboree-nintendo-switch-preview/)

        Sep 6, 2024 | 12:49 PM EDT
        
        ### [Gaming legend Jennifer Hale on X-Men ’97, AI concerns and ‘extraordinary’ Canadian talent](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/06/jennifer-hale-interview-x-men-97-ai-canadian-talent/)

        Sep 6, 2024 | 10:04 AM EDT
        
        ### [There were a lot of impressive Canadian indie games at PAX West 2024](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/06/canadian-indie-games-pax-west-2024/)

    Sep 23, 2024 | 6:57 PM EDT
    
    ### [Streaming in Canada on Crave, Disney+, Netflix and Prime Video \[Sept. 23-29\]](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/23/streaming-in-canada-crave-disney-plus-netflix-prime-video-will-and-harper/)

    Sep 21, 2024 | 2:27 PM EDT
    
    ### [Where to stream animated Transformers titles after Transformers One](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/21/where-to-stream-beasties-transformers-transformers-the-movie-in-canada/)

    Sep 21, 2024 | 10:57 AM EDT
    
    ### [Telecom news roundup: Rogers buys Bell’s MLSE stake, SaskTel takes on CRTC \[Sept. 14-20\]](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/21/telecom-news-roundup-rogers-bell-mlse-sasktel-crtc/)

    Sep 18, 2024 | 5:42 PM EDT
    
    ### [New on Crunchyroll: Fall 2024](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/18/new-on-crunchyroll-fall-2024/)

    Sep 18, 2024 | 9:34 AM EDT
    
    ### [Where to stream The Batman spin-off The Penguin in Canada](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/18/where-to-stream-batman-the-penguin-in-canada/)

    Sep 16, 2024 | 7:03 PM EDT
    
    ### [Streaming in Canada on Crave, Disney+, Netflix, Paramount+ and Prime Video \[Sept. 16-22\]](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/16/streaming-in-canada-crave-disney-plus-netflix-paramount-plus-prime-video-gord-downie-the-tragically-hip-no-dress-rehearsal/)

        Sep 21, 2024 | 10:57 AM EDT
        
        ### [Telecom news roundup: Rogers buys Bell’s MLSE stake, SaskTel takes on CRTC \[Sept. 14-20\]](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/21/telecom-news-roundup-rogers-bell-mlse-sasktel-crtc/)

        Sep 14, 2024 | 11:02 AM EDT
        
        ### [Telecom news roundup: Fido, Virgin, Koodo raise prices \[Sept. 6-13\]](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/14/telecom-news-roundup-fido-virgin-koodo-raise-prices/)

        Sep 13, 2024 | 10:37 AM EDT
        
        ### [Here’s how much the iPhone 16 series costs at Canadian carriers](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/13/canadian-carrier-iphone-16-pricing-bell-telus-rogers-freedom/)

        Sep 11, 2024 | 1:57 PM EDT
        
        ### [Here’s how the iPhone 16 series stacks up against its predecessors](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/11/iphone-16-series-vs-iphone-15-iphone-14/)

        Aug 31, 2024 | 11:07 AM EDT
        
        ### [Telecom news roundup: Telus raises connection fee to $70 \[Aug 24-30\]](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/08/31/telecom-news-roundup-telus-connection-fee/)

        Aug 20, 2024 | 11:31 AM EDT
        
        ### [Here are the big video game and streaming attractions at Fan Expo Canada 2024](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/08/20/fan-expo-canada-2024-video-game-streaming-programming-highlights/)

        Sep 23, 2024 | 6:57 PM EDT
        
        ### [Streaming in Canada on Crave, Disney+, Netflix and Prime Video \[Sept. 23-29\]](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/23/streaming-in-canada-crave-disney-plus-netflix-prime-video-will-and-harper/)

        Sep 21, 2024 | 2:27 PM EDT
        
        ### [Where to stream animated Transformers titles after Transformers One](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/21/where-to-stream-beasties-transformers-transformers-the-movie-in-canada/)

        Sep 18, 2024 | 5:42 PM EDT
        
        ### [New on Crunchyroll: Fall 2024](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/18/new-on-crunchyroll-fall-2024/)

        Sep 18, 2024 | 9:34 AM EDT
        
        ### [Where to stream The Batman spin-off The Penguin in Canada](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/18/where-to-stream-batman-the-penguin-in-canada/)

        Sep 16, 2024 | 7:03 PM EDT
        
        ### [Streaming in Canada on Crave, Disney+, Netflix, Paramount+ and Prime Video \[Sept. 16-22\]](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/16/streaming-in-canada-crave-disney-plus-netflix-paramount-plus-prime-video-gord-downie-the-tragically-hip-no-dress-rehearsal/)

        Sep 14, 2024 | 2:28 PM EDT
        
        ### [How to watch the September 2024 Emmy Awards in Canada](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/14/how-to-watch-september-2024-emmy-awards-in-canada/)

        Sep 9, 2024 | 9:57 AM EDT
        
        ### [How to watch Apple’s 2024 fall iPhone event](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/09/how-to-watch-apples-2024-fall-iphone-event/)

        Jun 10, 2024 | 4:44 PM EDT
        
        ### [Here’s how you can get your hands on iOS 18 today](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/06/10/how-to-download-ios-18-today/)

        Jun 7, 2024 | 8:05 AM EDT
        
        ### [How to watch Summer Game Fest, Xbox Games Showcase, Ubisoft Forward and more](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/06/07/how-to-watch-summer-game-fest-xbox-games-showcase-ubisoft-forward/)

        May 17, 2024 | 5:07 PM EDT
        
        ### [How to use RetroArch on your Apple TV](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/05/17/how-to-use-retroarch-on-your-apple-tv/)

        May 7, 2024 | 9:06 AM EDT
        
        ### [How to watch Apple’s ‘Let Loose’ iPad event](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/05/07/how-to-watch-apple-let-loose-ipad-event/)

        May 5, 2024 | 4:02 PM EDT
        
        ### [Avoid fake Delta apps on Android with these great emulators](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/05/05/fake-delta-app-android-best-emulators/)

    Sep 24, 2024 | 3:35 PM EDT
    
    ### [QueerTech brings annual QT conference to Toronto from Nov. 6-7](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/24/queertech-conference/)

    Sep 24, 2024 | 11:34 AM EDT
    
    ### [Ericsson expands Concordia partnership with 10-year agreement](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/24/ericsson-concordia-partnership-10-year-agreement/)

    Sep 18, 2024 | 3:49 PM EDT
    
    ### [SaskTel seeks judicial review of CRTC wholesale fibre access decision](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/18/sasktel-judicial-review-crtc-wholesale-access-fibre-decision/)

    Sep 18, 2024 | 12:30 PM EDT
    
    ### [Statistics Canada changes how it tracks wireless pricing](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/18/statistics-canada-changes-wireless-pricing-tracking/)

    Sep 18, 2024 | 11:11 AM EDT
    
    ### [Rogers buys out Bell stake in Leafs, Raptors parent company MLSE \[Update\]](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/18/rogers-buys-out-bell-stake-leaf-raptors-mlse/)

    Sep 17, 2024 | 6:04 PM EDT
    
    ### [Intel foundry business to make custom AI chip for AWS](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/17/intel-foundry-custom-ai-chip-aws/)

        Sep 24, 2024 | 3:35 PM EDT
        
        ### [QueerTech brings annual QT conference to Toronto from Nov. 6-7](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/24/queertech-conference/)

        Sep 24, 2024 | 11:34 AM EDT
        
        ### [Ericsson expands Concordia partnership with 10-year agreement](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/24/ericsson-concordia-partnership-10-year-agreement/)

        Sep 18, 2024 | 11:11 AM EDT
        
        ### [Rogers buys out Bell stake in Leafs, Raptors parent company MLSE \[Update\]](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/18/rogers-buys-out-bell-stake-leaf-raptors-mlse/)

        Sep 17, 2024 | 6:04 PM EDT
        
        ### [Intel foundry business to make custom AI chip for AWS](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/17/intel-foundry-custom-ai-chip-aws/)

        Sep 17, 2024 | 10:02 AM EDT
        
        ### [Quebecor offered to buy Corus, received no response: report](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/17/corus-no-response-quebecor-purchase-offer-report/)

        Sep 11, 2024 | 4:46 PM EDT
        
        ### [Samsung planning global layoffs up to 30 percent in some divisions: report](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/11/samsung-layoffs-30-percent-some-divisions-report/)

        Sep 18, 2024 | 3:49 PM EDT
        
        ### [SaskTel seeks judicial review of CRTC wholesale fibre access decision](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/18/sasktel-judicial-review-crtc-wholesale-access-fibre-decision/)

        Sep 18, 2024 | 12:30 PM EDT
        
        ### [Statistics Canada changes how it tracks wireless pricing](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/18/statistics-canada-changes-wireless-pricing-tracking/)

        Sep 6, 2024 | 11:04 AM EDT
        
        ### [Donald Trump suggests assigning Elon Musk to ‘government efficiency’ commission](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/06/donald-trump-suggests-assigning-elon-musk-to-government-efficiency-commission/)

        Sep 3, 2024 | 2:20 PM EDT
        
        ### [Online Canadian SIN card applications now only take five days](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/03/online-sin-card-applications-wait-time-reduced/)

        Aug 14, 2024 | 12:50 PM EDT
        
        ### [U.S. DOJ reportedly considering breaking Google up](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/08/14/us-doj-considering-breaking-google-up/)

        Aug 7, 2024 | 9:46 AM EDT
        
        ### [Saskatchewan is the latest province to announce a phone ban in classrooms](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/08/07/saskatchewan-phone-ban-classrooms/)

        May 22, 2024 | 12:22 PM EDT
        
        ### [U.K. looking into Microsoft’s Recall feature over privacy concerns](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/05/22/uk-ico-microsoft-recall-privacy-concerns/)

        Apr 30, 2024 | 9:25 AM EDT
        
        ### [London Drugs temporarily closes stores following cyberattack](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/04/30/london-drugs-temporarily-closes-stores-cyberattack/)

        Apr 22, 2024 | 5:56 PM EDT
        
        ### [Nothing customer data leaked after apparent breach](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/04/22/nothing-customer-data-leak-breach/)

        Apr 12, 2024 | 12:29 PM EDT
        
        ### [New Roku breach impacted 576,000 accounts, less than 400 actually compromised](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/04/12/roku-breach-impacted-576000-accounts/)

        Apr 4, 2024 | 9:07 PM EDT
        
        ### [Google takes down 87 fake investment/crypto apps that scammed victims out of thousands](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/04/04/google-play-store-fake-investment-crypto-apps/)

        Mar 28, 2024 | 8:00 AM EDT
        
        ### [A new wave of Apple phishing attacks is targeting users](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/03/28/a-new-wave-of-apple-phishing-attack-is-targeting-users/)

        Sep 17, 2024 | 3:48 PM EDT
        
        ### [Bell, MacLean collaborate on remote mining vehicle technology](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/17/bell-maclean-mining-technology-collaboration/)

        Sep 16, 2024 | 6:08 PM EDT
        
        ### [Musk says Canada-wide Starlink would cost ‘less than half’ of $2.1 billion Telesat deal](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/16/elon-musk-canada-starlink-less-than-half-federal-government-telesat-deal/)

        Jul 19, 2024 | 9:29 AM EDT
        
        ### [Global IT outage disrupts airports, banks, healthcare and more](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/07/19/global-it-outage-disrupts-airports-banks-and-other-businesses/)

        Jul 12, 2024 | 4:52 PM EDT
        
        ### [Copper thieves increasingly targeting telecom equipment in Canada](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/07/12/copper-thieves-increasingly-targeting-telecom-equipment-in-canada/)

        May 22, 2024 | 12:33 PM EDT
        
        ### [Canada has the cheapest broadband internet prices in North America: report](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/05/22/canada-cheapest-broadband-internet-prices-north-america-report/)

        Apr 24, 2024 | 11:15 AM EDT
        
        ### [Rogers is bringing Comcast and Xfinity products to Canada](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/04/24/rogers-bringing-comcast-xfinity-products-services-canada/)

    Sep 24, 2024 | 9:01 AM EDT
    
    ### [Roku Ultra + Voice Remote bundle is now available for pre-order](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/24/roku-ultra-voice-remote-bundle/)

    Sep 20, 2024 | 1:33 PM EDT
    
    ### [Arcane’s final season gets staggered release on Netflix in November](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/20/netflix-arcane-november-final-season-staggered-release/)

    Sep 19, 2024 | 4:33 PM EDT
    
    ### [MrBeast and Amazon sued by contestants over Beast Games series](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/19/mrbeast-amazon-sued-contestants-beast-games-series/)

    Sep 17, 2024 | 3:01 PM EDT
    
    ### [Heartstopper season 3 trailer reveals October 3 release date](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/17/heartstopper-season-3-trailer-october-3/)

    Sep 16, 2024 | 1:47 PM EDT
    
    ### [Flappy Bird creator says he has nothing to do with crypto-filled revival](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/16/new-flappy-bird-crypto-no-ties-original-creator/)

    Sep 9, 2024 | 12:52 PM EDT
    
    ### [Studio Ghibli’s The Boy and the Heron hits Netflix Canada in October](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/09/studio-ghibli-hayao-miyazaki-the-boy-and-the-heron-netflix-canada-premiere-date/)

        Sep 24, 2024 | 9:01 AM EDT
        
        ### [Roku Ultra + Voice Remote bundle is now available for pre-order](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/24/roku-ultra-voice-remote-bundle/)

        Sep 20, 2024 | 1:33 PM EDT
        
        ### [Arcane’s final season gets staggered release on Netflix in November](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/20/netflix-arcane-november-final-season-staggered-release/)

        Sep 19, 2024 | 4:33 PM EDT
        
        ### [MrBeast and Amazon sued by contestants over Beast Games series](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/19/mrbeast-amazon-sued-contestants-beast-games-series/)

        Sep 17, 2024 | 3:01 PM EDT
        
        ### [Heartstopper season 3 trailer reveals October 3 release date](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/17/heartstopper-season-3-trailer-october-3/)

        Sep 16, 2024 | 1:47 PM EDT
        
        ### [Flappy Bird creator says he has nothing to do with crypto-filled revival](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/16/new-flappy-bird-crypto-no-ties-original-creator/)

        Sep 9, 2024 | 12:52 PM EDT
        
        ### [Studio Ghibli’s The Boy and the Heron hits Netflix Canada in October](https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/09/09/studio-ghibli-hayao-miyazaki-the-boy-and-the-heron-netflix-canada-premiere-date/)

[](javascript:void(0))

Privacy Policy
==============

**Last Updated: December 4, 2023**

### Introduction

Blue Ant Media Inc. respects the privacy of all of its users and customers and is committed to protecting such privacy in accordance with this Privacy Policy. This policy explains Blue Ant Media Inc.’s and its subsidiaries’ and affiliates’ (collectively, “**Blue Ant Media**“) treatment of your personally identifiable information collected in connection with your activities on or related to all Blue Ant Media websites referencing this policy (the “**Blue Ant Media Sites**“) and any services made available on the Blue Ant Media Sites (collectively, unless noted otherwise, the “**Blue Ant Media Services**“). We urge you to read this policy carefully and to check back periodically for changes, which will indicate the latest revision date. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies or websites that are not owned or controlled by Blue Ant Media.

### What Personal Information Do We Collect?

In the course of operating any Blue Ant Media Services, we may collect two types of information about our users and customers: Personal Information and Non-Personal Information.

“**Personal Information**” is personally identifiable information, such as your name, address, email address, birth date and gender. Personal Information is collected by us when you choose to provide it to us when registering for a Blue Ant Media Service, such as when you choose to subscribe to a Blue Ant Media Service or newsletter, or enter a Blue Ant Media promotion. In addition, if you choose to contact a customer service representative of ours or provide us with feedback, we may keep a record of that correspondence so that we may fully address the subject matter. We may also receive Personal Information from our business partners and other third parties, provided that such third parties confirm to us that you have permitted them to share such information. Business contact information such as the name, title, business address, email address or telephone number of a business or professional person or an employee of an organization is not considered Personal Information.

“**Account Information**” is information that may be required to set up an Account on a Blue Ant Media Site (as more fully described in the Terms and Conditions). For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, Account Information is also Personal Information.

“**Non-Personal Information**” is information that is not linked to a specific person. This includes technical information such as your Internet Protocol Address, the domain you may have used to access a Blue Ant Media Service, the type and version of browser or operating system you may be using, and the website you may have come from and visit next. Aggregate information, such as the demographic statistics of our users and customers (e.g. average age or geographical allocation of our users), number of visitors and average time spent on a Blue Ant Media Service, is also considered Non-Personal Information. Non-Personal Information is collected or derived by us in the course of operating a Blue Ant Media Service. For example, our web servers may automatically collect Non-Personal Information that is provided through your browser or stored on a Cookie or through a Web Beacon when you choose to visit a Blue Ant Media Service.  We may also receive Non-Personal Information about you from third-party business partners and other service providers which may include video view.  We may collect Non-Personal Information automatically via cookies (as set out in the How do we use Cookies and Web Beacons below).  Where the cookies are not strictly necessary to provide a Blue Ant Media Service, then we will only collect information about you from such cookies with your consent.

### How Do We Use Your Personal Information?

We may use Personal Information for the following purposes:

a) Providing you with a Blue Ant Media Service and information you have requested from us, including your use of a Blue Ant Media Site. We may from time to time use your Personal Information to contact you about changes, enhancements or similar notices related to a Blue Ant Media Service;

b) If you opted-into receiving offers or information from us or certain of our selected sponsors or advertisers, we may send you email materials and other mailings about products and services that we feel may be of interest to you. If at any time you would like to end your subscription to any such email materials, follow the directions posted at the bottom of the email or the relevant website;

c) If you enter a contest or other promotion offered on a Blue Ant Media Site, we may, under the rules of the promotion, use your name and certain other information to administer the promotion, such as contacting, announcing and promoting the winners of the promotion;

d) We may also use Personal Information if we have reasonable grounds to believe the information could be useful when investigating a contravention of a federal, provincial, foreign or other law or in order to protect or defend a legal interest; and

e) Account Information is used to manage your Account, to verify your credentials for logging-in to the Blue Ant Media Site or Blue Ant Media Service associated with the Account, and to communicate with you information about your Account when necessary.

We must have legal basis to process your Personal Information.  In most cases, the legal basis will be one of the following:

* Your consent to our processing;
* To fulfill our contractual obligations to you
* To comply with our legal obligations
* To meet our legitimate interests to run our business effectively, to understand how you use our services and to enable us to derive knowledge from that to enable us to develop new services and keep our records accurate and up to date. When we process your personal information to meet our legitimate interests, we put in place robust safeguards to ensure that your privacy is protected and to ensure that our legitimate interests are not overridden by your interests or fundamental rights and freedoms.

### Disclosure of Your Personal Information

We will not sell or rent your Personal Information to any third party.

We will only disclose your Personal Information to third parties under the following circumstances:

a) Where you have specifically given us your consent to disclose your Personal Information for a designated purpose;

b) To persons acting on our behalf as our agents, suppliers or service providers, solely to enable us to more efficiently provide you with a Blue Ant Media Service. Such entities act under strict contractual controls, requiring them to maintain the confidentiality of all such Personal Information and to use such information solely for purposes related to the provision of the Blue Ant Media Services;

c) As may be set out in the Terms and Conditions applicable to Blue Ant Media Service to facilitate the provision of such service, such as fulfilling legal requirements;

d) As required by law, including by an order of any court, institution or body with jurisdiction or authority to compel the production of information, or in order to protect or defend a legal interest; or

e) In connection with a Blue Ant Media corporate re-organization, merger, amalgamation or similar transaction with another entity, or a sale of all or a substantial portion of the assets of Blue Ant Media, provided that the Personal Information disclosed continues to be used for the purposes permitted by this policy by the entity acquiring the information.

For our Quebec users and visitors, we endeavour to keep your Personal Information in Quebec. However, certain of our service providers (and Blue Ant Media) are in other provinces or countries where your Personal Information may be transferred. When this happens, we will perform what Quebec’s Act Respecting the Protection of Personal Information in the Private Sector (the “Quebec Private Sector Act”) calls an “Assessment of the privacy-related factors” (what is generally called a “Privacy Impact Assessment,” or “PIA”) prior to the Personal Information leaving Quebec. If the PIA does not meet our standards and the standards required by the Quebec Private Sector Act, we will not transfer your Personal Information.

### Your rights over your Personal Information

You have certain rights regarding your Personal Information, subject to local law. These include the following rights to:

* withdraw your consent to our processing of your Personal Information;
* access your Personal Information;
* rectify the Personal Information we hold about you;
* erase your Personal Information;
* restrict our use of your Personal Information;
* object to our use of your Personal Information;
* receive your Personal Information in a usable electronic format and transmit it to a third party (right to data portability);
* lodge a complaint with your local data protection authority.

If you would like to discuss or exercise such rights, please contact us at the details below.  You may also exercise these rights by contacting our Data Protection Officer listed in that same section below.

We encourage you to contact us to update or correct your information if it changes or if the Personal Information we hold about you is inaccurate. Where you have provided your consent to any use of your Personal Information, you can withdraw this consent at any time.

We will contact you if we need additional information from you in order to honour your requests.

If you no longer wish to receive non-transactional communications from us, please click the “unsubscribe” link in any email from us, update your marketing preferences in your account, or contact us at the address below.

### How Do We Use Non-Personal Information?

Non-Personal Information is collected or derived by us in the course of operating the Blue Ant Media Services. In addition to our practices related to IP addresses, Cookies or Web Beacons, Non-Personal Information is used generally by us to monitor and improve the operation of our services, to perform statistical analyses of the collective characteristics and behavior of our users and customers, to measure user demographics and interests regarding specific Blue Ant Media Services, to describe our services to third parties such as prospective business partners and advertisers, and to analyze how and where best to use our resources. No Personal Information will be disclosed during these activities.

We may also use Non-Personal Information to inform our sponsors and advertisers as to the performance of a particular sponsorship (such as a contest) or advertisement. In any such case, we may disclose to those third party sponsors and advertisers the overall aggregate demographics available regarding, for example, who participated in a contest or who saw and “clicked” on an advertisement. No Personal Information will be disclosed to these sponsors and advertisers as part of this process; only information in an anonymous, aggregate form will be disclosed.

### How Do We Use Cookies and Web Beacons?

A cookie is a small text file containing a unique identification number that is transferred (through your browser) from a web site to the hard drive of your computer or device. The cookie identifies your browser and will not let a web site know any personal information about you, such as your name and address. Since cookies are only text files, they cannot run on your computer or device, search your computer or device for other information, or transmit any information to anyone. Cookies are used on many major web sites. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. If you prefer, you can reset your browser either to notify you when you have received a cookie, or to refuse to accept cookies. You should understand that while we do not require you to use cookies, certain of our services will not function properly if you set your browser to not accept cookies.

Blue Ant Media may use cookies to:

a) Monitor website usage and improve the operation and performance of our and to make our services easier and more convenient to use. For example, cookies help us to remember who you are through your browser settings so that we can offer and provide more personalized services (e.g. language preference). Cookies also allow us to save passwords and preferences and other login information for you so that you will not have to re-enter them the next time you visit a Blue Ant Media Service to sign into your Account;

b) Measure aggregate user traffic and demographic statistics related to the Blue Ant Media Services and advertisements (e.g. number of users, average time spent, average age and similar statistics). This information helps us to better understand when to update, change or offer new services and provides us with details as to the performance of third party advertisements and content. This information may be reported, in aggregate form only, to our current and prospective sponsors, advertisers and business partners. No Personal Information will be disclosed in such reports; and

c) Displaying advertisements. Blue Ant Media and third party advertising providers used by us may use cookies when serving advertisements.

Certain Blue Ant Media Services may contain electronic images known as Web Beacons – sometimes called single-pixel gifs – that allow us to count users and customers who have visited those pages and to deliver co-branded services. Web Beacons are not used to access your Personal Information; they are a technique used to compile aggregated statistics about Blue Ant Media Service usage. Web Beacons collect only a limited set of information, including a cookie number, time and date of a page view, and a description of the page on which the Web Beacon resides. Certain Blue Ant Media Service web pages may also contain Web Beacons placed there by our advertising partners to help us determine the effectiveness of our Internet advertising campaigns.

The following table sets out the different categories of cookies that the Blue Ant Media Services use and why we use them.

| Type of Cookie \[Purpose\] | Source \[Company\] | What these cookies do | How to exercise your cookie choices |
| --- | --- | --- | --- |
| Newsletter cookies | Mailchimp | We use Mailchimp to send to deliver our email newsletter program. You receive newsletters when you provide opt-in consent. | More information on Mailchimp, including details on how to opt-out, is available [here](https://www.intuit.com/privacy/statement/). |
| Analytics cookies | Google AnalyticsComScore | We use Google Analytics to collect information on how the Blue Ant Media Services are used and to report on usage statistics.We use Comscore to collect information about how the Blue Ant Media Services are used and to provide marketing data | More information on Google Analytics, including details on how to opt-out, is available [here](http://www.google.co.uk/intl/en/policies/privacy/partners/).More information on ComScore cookies is available [here](https://www.comscore.com/About-comScore/Privacy-Policy). |
| Social media cookies | TwitterFacebook<br><br>Instagram<br><br>Pinterest | We use Twitter to communicate and share relevant information.We use Facebook to communicate with our fans and share relevant information. We also use Facebook to deliver advertising and we ensure that our advertisements are relevant to you and to help you share your experiences with the Blue Ant Media Services with your contacts on Facebook.<br><br>We use Instagram to communicate with our fans and share relevant information. We also use Instagram to deliver advertising and we ensure that our advertisements are relevant to you.<br><br>We use Pinterest to communicate with our fans and share relevant information. We also use Pinterest to deliver advertising and we ensure that our advertisements are relevant to you. | More information on Twitter cookies is available [here.](https://help.twitter.com/en/rules-and-policies/x-cookies)More information on Facebook cookies is available [here](https://www.facebook.com/privacy/policies/cookies/?entry_point=cookie_policy_redirect&entry=0).<br><br>More information on Instagram cookies is available [here](https://help.instagram.com/155833707900388).<br><br>More information on Pinterest cookies is available [here](https://policy.pinterest.com/en/privacy-policy). |
| Advertising cookies | Google Ad ManagerSortable<br><br>STN Video<br><br>Magnite | We use Google Ad Manager to run our website advertisements for both direct and programmatic advertising clients.We use Sortable to manage our website programmatic advertising program.<br><br>We use STN Video to run our pre-roll advertisements for both direct and programmatic advertising clients <br><br>We use Magnite to run our outstream advertisements for both direct and programmatic advertising clients | More information on Google Ad Manager cookies is available [here.](https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en)  More information on Sortable cookies is available [here](https://sortable.com/privacy-policy/)[.](https://docs.sortable.com/privacy-policy/) <br><br>More information on STN Video cookies is available [here.](https://www.stnvideo.com/cookie-policy/)<br><br>More information about Magnite cookies is available [here.](https://www.magnite.com/legal/website-cookie-platform-policy/) |
| Video Player cookies | BrightcoveSTN Video | We use Brightcove to run our onsite videos.We use STN Video to run our onsite videos | More information about Brightcove is [here.](https://www.brightcove.com/en/legal/privacy)  More information on STN Video cookies is available [here.](https://www.stnvideo.com/cookie-policy/) |

You have the right to choose whether or not to accept cookies.  However, they are an important part of how the Blue Ant Media Services work, so you should be aware that if you choose to refuse or remove cookies, this could affect the availability and functionality of the Blue Ant Media Services.

Most web browsers are set to accept cookies by default.  If you prefer, you can usually choose to set your browser to remove or reject browser cookies.  To do so, please follow the instructions provided by your browser which are usually located within the “Help”, “Tools” or “Edit” facility.  Some third parties also provide the ability to refuse their cookies directly by clicking on an opt-out link, and we have indicated where this is possible in the table above.

### What IP Address Information is Collected and How is It Used?

An IP address is the unique number that is assigned to every direct Internet access point. Many IP addresses can generally be associated with certain Internet service providers or large organizations. When you, through your browser, request a web page or similar Internet information from another computer on the Internet, your browser automatically provides that computer with an IP address to which it will send the requested information.

Whenever you request a Blue Ant Media Service web page or certain other similar Blue Ant Media content, your browser automatically provides our computers with your IP address, to which our computers will send the requested information. Each such request is logged by our computers with information including the IP address of the computer that requested the page and is stored by our computers as needed for the purposes described in this policy.

We may use your IP address to display more appropriate and relevant content and advertising, such as content and advertising based on your geographic area. Aggregate information derived from IP addresses may be reported by us to our advertisers and partners. For example, we may report to our advertisers the estimated total number of users accessing a particular Blue Ant Media Site from a specific province. We may also use your IP address to facilitate the diagnoses and remedy of a technical problem reported by you or our technical team.

### What Privacy Applies to the Forums on the Site?

Blue Ant Media Sites may feature chat board or forums (collectively “**Forums**“) that enable our users to communicate with each other. Blue Ant Media does not moderate and is not responsible for the content that you or any user posts on any Forum. All Personal Information you post in a Forum becomes public information and may be viewed, collected and used by any visitor to the Site, and may expose you to unsolicited messages. Blue Ant Media strongly recommends that you do not post on any Forum private information about yourself or other individuals.

### What Privacy Applies to User Content?

Some Blue Ant Media Sites may allow for users to post or upload User Content, as more specifically outlined and defined in the Terms and Conditions. Blue Ant Media may or may not edit, curate, moderate or otherwise check posted or uploaded User Content (depending on the Blue Ant Media Site), and is not responsible for the User Content that you or any user posts or uploads on any Blue Ant Media Site. All Personal Information you post or upload as part of your User Content becomes public information and may be viewed, collected and used by any visitor to the Blue Ant Media Site on which the User Content is posted. Blue Ant Media strongly recommends that you do not post or upload private information about yourself or other individuals in your User Content.

As outlined in the [Terms and Conditions](https://blueantmedia.com/terms-and-conditions/), your username may be attached to your User Content which Blue Ant Media may distribute and display through third parties. We thus encourage you to consider limiting the amount of Personal Information revealed in your username. Furthermore, if you choose to attach your real name to your posted User Content (as may be permitted by some of the Blue Ant Media Services), this will be available for all Blue Ant Media Site visitors and third parties to view, and you consent to the use of your name in this manner.

### What Privacy Applies to Business Partners’ and Third Party Web Sites?

The Blue Ant Media Sites contains links from and to sites operated by our business partners and other independent third parties. Once you leave a Blue Ant Media Site, you may or may not see a new URL in the location bar. Please review the linked site’s and third party content provider’s privacy policies, and if you do not agree to be bound by the terms of the policies governing that provider/site, terminate your use of that service or your visit to the site. The linked sites are not under our influence or control, and we are not responsible for the privacy policies and practices or the content of the sites operated by our business partners or other third parties or the privacy policies and practices or contents of any linked site or subsequent links from that site.

### How Do We Secure Your Information?

We have policies and procedures in place to protect the privacy and confidentiality of your information that we collect and maintain, including contracts with third parties that manage the information provided by you. All Personal Information is stored on secured servers, behind a firewall at a data centre with access to data strictly controlled. Only individuals specifically involved in the analysis and other functions set out herein have access to your Personal Information. These individuals have been provided the requisite training on our privacy policies and practices, and are under contractual or legal obligations not to share your Personal Information with any third party or use it for any other purpose not described in this privacy policy.

To help ensure the privacy of your Personal Information, we urge you not to share your user name and password with anyone and recommend that you change your password frequently and store it in a safe place. If you are asked to create a user name or password, please select words that do not personally identify you. We may offer “auto login” which allows users to enter member areas of a Blue Ant Media Site without re-entering password information. You may want to disable auto login on your “Set Up” page if you are not the only person using your computer.

We will keep your Personal Information for as long as we have a relationship with you. Once our relationship with you has come to an end, we will retain your Personal Information for a period of time that enables us to:

* Maintain business records for analysis and/or audit purposes
* Comply with record retention requirements under the law
* Defend or bring any existing or potential legal claims
* Deal with any complaints regarding the Blue Ant Media Services

We will delete your Personal Information when it is no longer required for these purposes. If there is any information that we are unable, for technical reasons, to delete entirely from our systems, we will put in place appropriate measures to prevent any further processing or use of the data. We may also anonymize your Personal Information, when permitted to do so under applicable privacy and data protection laws.

In addition, we have drafted and implemented certain internal procedures and policies regarding Personal Information, including the following: (i) a framework for the keeping and destruction of the Personal Information, including where we may keep anonymized data; (ii) defining and describing the roles and responsibilities of the members of Blue Ant Media personnel throughout the life cycle of the Personal Information; (iii) process for dealing with individual complaints and requests for Personal Information and exercising of the individual’s rights under privacy laws; and (iv) a management and IT policy and procedure for addressing potential data breach incidents involving Personal Information in the custody of Blue Ant Media.

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

You may request a copy of this privacy policy from us using the contact details set out below. We may modify or update this privacy notice from time to time.

Any changes we may make to this privacy policy in the future will be posted on this page and, where appropriate, notified to you by e-mail. Please check back frequently to see any updates or changes to this privacy policy.

Where changes to this privacy policy will have a fundamental impact on the nature of the processing or otherwise have a substantial impact on you, we will give you sufficient advance notice so that you have the opportunity to exercise your rights (e.g. object to the processing).

### How Can We Be Contacted About Our Privacy Policy and Practices?

If you have any concerns about privacy procedures at any Blue Ant Media Site, wish to find out further details about how your Personal Information may be used, want to update your Personal Information, or exercise any of your available rights regarding your Person Information write us at:

Blue Ant Media Inc.  
99 Atlantic Avenue  
Suite 400  
Toronto, Ontario  
M6K 3J8

OR

c/o McCarthy Tetrault  
18th Floor  
1 Angel Court  
London EC2R 7HJ  
United Kingdom

Or you may email us at [privacy@blueantmedia.com](mailto:%20privacy@blueantmedia.com)

_Data Protection Officer_

In addition to the contact information above, further to the European General Data Protection Regulation (“GDPR”) and the Quebec Private Sector Act we have designated a Data Protection Officer (“DPO”) who is ultimately responsible for all personal data matters at Blue Ant Media.  If you have a specific complaint regarding your personal data or wish to invoke your legal rights under the GDPR or the Quebec Private Sector Act, you can contact our DPO directly:

Astrid Zimmer  

Mailing address same as Toronto, Canada address above

#### Categories

#### Contact us

#### Social

#### Newsletter Signup

© 2024 ZoomerMedia [Privacy.](https://mobilesyrup.com/privacy-policy/) [Terms of use.](https://mobilesyrup.com/terms-and-conditions/)
